Ok...
好了
The X10's are online
这台X10已经连上网了
Gentlemen, I am now about to send a signal
from this laptop through our local ISP
先生们 接下来我要从这台笔记本发出信号
通过本地ISP
racing down fibre optic cable at
the speed of light to San Fransisco,
经由光纤电缆 以光速直达旧金山
bouncing off a satellite in
geosynchronous orbit to Lisbon, Portugal,
通过地球同步卫星的反射
到达葡萄牙的里斯本
where the data packets will be headed off
to submerge transatlantic cables,
然后数据包就会直通
跨大西洋海底电缆
terminating in Halifax, Nova Scotia
在新斯科舍省的哈利法克斯暂歇之后
(位于加拿大)
and transfered across the continent
via microwave relays back to our ISP
跨越整个大陆
通过微波传送回我们的ISP
And the extend receiver attached to this...
而扩展接收器就安在这个...
Lamp.
灯
Look at me, look at me. I've got goosebumps.
看看我 看看我
我都起鸡皮疙瘩了
- Are we ready for the stereo?
- Go for stereo.
- 立体声准备好了吗?
- 试试看音响
- Hey guys.
- Hello.
- 嘿 大家
- 你好
It's a little loud.
有点吵哎
No problem...
Turning it down.
没问题... 声音关小点
San Francisco, Lisbon, Halifax...
...et voil?
旧金山 里斯本 哈利法克斯...
这样好了?
- OK, thanks.
- Hang on, hang on. Do you not
realise what we just did?
- 好 谢谢
- 等下 你没注意到我们刚才做的事吗?
Yeah, you turned your stereo down with your laptop.
注意到了
你们刚刚用笔记本调低了音响声音
No, we turned our stereo down, by sending
a signal around the world via the Internet.
不 我们是借由网络向全球发出了信号
然后使立体声音量变小
Oh. You know you can get one of those
universal remotes from Radioshack?
你们可以买个Radioshack的万能遥控
(美国第三大电子零售商)
They're really cheap.
那个非常便宜
No, you don't get it.
Howard,
不 你没明白
Howard
- Enable public access.
- Public access enabled.
- 打开公共通道
- 公共通道已打开
- Boy, that's terrific. I'll see ya.
- No hang on, hang on...
- 棒极了 回见
- 不 等等...
See?
看到没?
No.
没啊
Someone in Sichuan province,
China, is using his computer
有个人在中国的四川省
正在用他的电脑
to turn our lights on and off.
来操控我们灯的开和关
Oh, that's handy.
哦 那还真挺方便的
Here's a question...
Why?
我有个问题...
为什么这么做?
Because we can.
因为我们能做到
They found our remote control cars!
他们发现我们的遥控车了!
- Wait, what's on top of that?
- Wireless webcams, wave hello!
- 等一下 那个上面是什么?
- 无线摄像头 打个招呼!
The monster truck is out of Austin, Texas,
那辆怪兽卡车由德州奥斯汀的某人操控
(即驶向Penny的三辆模型车)
and the blue Viper is being operated
from suburban Tel Aviv.
而那辆蓝色的道奇蝰蛇
由特拉维夫市郊(以色列某市)某人操控
- You may want to put on slacks.
- What?
- 你或许该穿条裤子
- 什么?
Ew, stop it! No!
Leave me alone!
恶 停下! 不!
离我远点!
- Who's running the red Corvette?
- That would be me.
- 谁在操纵那个红色巡洋舰?
- 是我
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
proudly presents
-=伊甸园美剧 http://sfile.ydy.com=-
荣誉出品
本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业途径
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
sync:
-=YTET-伊甸园字幕组=-
翻译: Violamo Lauracai
校对: 小猴宝宝
The Big Bang Theory
Season01 Episode09
天才理论传
第一季 第9集
You know in the future,
when we're disembodied brains in jars,
或许将来 当我们变成被放在罐子里的
脱离躯体的大脑时
we're going to look at this as eight hours well wasted.
回头看这八个小时 会是完全浪费
I don't want to be in a jar.
I want my brain in an android body.
我可不希望被放在罐子里
我希望我的大脑放在机器人体内
Eight feet tall and ribbed.
八英尺高 肋骨分明
I'm with you.
我支持你
I just have to make sure if I'm
a synthetic human I'd still be Jewish.
我只是想确保就算我成了人造人
我仍然是犹太人
I promised my mother.
我答应过我妈妈
I suppose you could have
your android penis circumcised.
我觉得你还可能得
给你的人工阴茎进行隔礼
But that's something your rabbi
would have to discuss with the manufacturer.
但那是你的犹太导师和制造商
应该探讨的问题
Not to mention you'd have to
power down on saturdays.
而且你星期六还得进入节电模式
(犹太人周末不工作 为安息日)
Sheldon, why is this letter in the trash?
Sheldon 这封信为啥在垃圾箱里?
Well, there's always the possibility that
嗯 不能排除说
a trash can spontaneously formed around the letter
那封信周围自然形成了一个垃圾桶
but Occam's rasor would suggest
that someone threw it out.
但据奥卡姆剃刀原理 应该是谁扔进去的吧
(原理核心 "如无必要 勿增实体")
It's from the Institute of
Experimental Physics, they want us to
这是物理实验研究所寄来的
他们想让我们
present our paper on the properties of supersolids
在玻色-爱因斯坦凝聚体主题会上
at the topical conference of Bose-Einstein condensates.
发表我们关于超立体特质的研究论文
I know.
I read it before I threw it out.
我知道
我把它扔掉之前读过了
Ok, if I may drill down to the bedrock of my question:
好吧 容我打破砂锅问到底
why did you throw it out?
你为什么把它扔掉?
Because I have no interest in standing in
the Rose room of the Pasadena Marriot,
因为我对站在
帕萨迪纳万豪酒店的玫瑰房里
in front of a group of judgmental strangers
面对一帮品头论足的陌生人
毫无兴趣
who wouldn't recognise true genius if
it was standing in front of them giving a speech.
就算一个真正的天才在面前讲演
他们也绝对察觉不到
Which if I were there, would be.
如果我在那儿的话 就会这样的
I don't know Sheldon.
我不明白 Sheldon
Those topical conferences on
Bose-Einstein condensates' parties are legendary
玻色-爱因斯坦凝聚体主题会的
派对可是传奇性的啊!
- Forget the parties!
- Forget the parties? What a nerd.
- 别提那些派对了!
- 别提那些派对了? 书呆子!
Are there any other honours I've got that I don't know about?
还有其他我不知情的荣誉吗?
Did the UPS dropped off a
Nobel prize with my name on it?
快递公司有没有送来一封
写着我名字的诺贝尔获奖信?
Leonard, please don't take this the wrong way,
but the day you win a Nobel prize,
Leonard 请别误会
但是什么时候你能得诺贝尔奖
is the day I begin my research on the drag coefficient of tassles on flying carpets.
我就什么时候开始对
飞毯流苏的药物共作用性研究
the only thing missing from that insult was: "your mama".
这个羞辱只漏了一点 就是"你妈妈"
I got one...
Hey Leonard,
我有个...
嗨 Leonard
- Your mama's research methodology is so flawed...
- Shut up, Howard.
- 你妈妈的研究方法论也太次了...
- 闭嘴 Howard
- Sheldon, we have to do this.
- No, we don't.
- Sheldon 我们必须去
- 不 没必要
We have to take a nourishment, to expel waste,
我们必须摄取营养 排泄废物
and inhale enough oxygen to keep our cells from dying.
吸取足够的氧气来保持细胞活性
Everything else is optional.
剩下的都是可选的
Ok, let me put it this way:
I'm doing it.
好吧 我这么说吧
我要去
You can't. I'm the lead author.
你不能 我才是主笔
Come on, the only reason you're the lead author is because we went alphabetically.
得了吧 那是因为你姓氏字母靠前
I let you think we went alphabetically to spare you
我让你以为我们是按字母排序
是为了减轻你的屈辱感
the humiliation with dealing with the fact that it was my idea.
免于承受"那论文是我的构思"
这个残酷的现实
Now to put too fine a point to it, but I was throwing you a bone.
坦率的说 我是在施恩于你
You're welcome.
不用谢了
Excuse me, I designed the experiment that proved the hypothesis.
拜托 是我设计了实验
证明了那些假设
That doesn't mean proving.
那才不是证明
So the entire scientific community is just supposed to take your word?
所以整个科学界都理应相信你的鬼话了?
They're not supposed to, but they should.
不是理应 他们应该相信
Alright, I don't care what you say.
好吧 我不管你怎么说
I'm going to the conference and
I'm presenting our findings
我会去参加这个会议
并且要发表我们的新发现
And I forbid it.
我不准
You forbid it?
你不准?
If I'm not taking credit for our work then nobody is.
如果这荣誉不是归我名下
那就谁也别想得到
- So, you admit that it's our work.
- No.
- 你承认这是我们共同的成果了
- 不是
Once again, I'm throwing
you a bone.
再说一遍 是我施恩于你
And once again, you are welcome.
再说一遍 不用谢了
So, how's it going with Sheldon?
Are you guys still not talking to each other?
你现在和Sheldon怎么样?
还是不说话吗?
Not only is he still not talking to me,
他不仅不和我说话
but there's this thing he does where he stares
at you and  tries to get your brain to explode.
他还总瞪着我
想要把我的头给看爆炸
You know, like in the classic sci-fi movie "Scanners"?
就像是那个经典的科幻电影"扫描机"
Like.... Bzzz.
就像....卟..
Nevermind.
算了
How about this one?
这件怎么样?
It says, I know my physics, but I'm still a fun guy.
它就像在说 我虽然精通物理
但我仍是一个风趣的人
Oh, I didn't know they still made corduroy suits.
哦 我不知道还有人生产灯芯绒西服
They don't, that's why I saved this one.
没人生产了 所以我留着这件
Ok, well, let's just see what else you have.
好的 咱们再看看你还有什么
Ok, here. Take this.
好 这儿 拿着这件
and this, and this,
and this, and these...
还有这件 这件
这件 还有这些...
Is this all stuff you want me to try on?
这些都是你想让我试穿的?
No, this is stuff I want you to throw out.
不 这些都是我想让你扔掉的
Seriously, don't even give it to charity,
you won't be helping anyone.
说真的 也别捐给慈善机构了
不会帮到任何人的
What's this?
这是什么?
That's the bottled city of Kandor.
这是瓶中城市Kandor
(出自"超人")
You see, Kandor was the
capital city of the planet Krypton.
Kandor曾是氪星球的首都
It was miniaturised by Brainiac before Krypton exploded
在氪星球爆炸之前
它被Brainiac缩小了
and then rescued by Superman.
然后被超人所拯救
Oh, nice.
哦 厉害
It's a lot cooler when girls aren't looking at it.
在没有女孩看的时候 它会更酷的
Here, why don't you put these while I find
a shirt and a sport cut match.
你先把它换上
我找找相配的衬衫和外套
Right, be right back.
好的 我马上回来
Where are you going? Just put them on.
你去哪? 穿上就行了
Here?
在这儿?
Oh, are you shy?
噢 你害羞了?
- No, I'm not shy.
- Don't worry I won't look.
- 不 我没害羞
- 别担心 我不会偷看的
I know you won't look.
Why would you look?
我知道你不会偷看
你为啥要偷看呢?
There's nothing to see...
Well, not 'nothing'...
又没什么好看的...
呃 也不是一点没有...
Sweetie, put the pants on.
亲爱的 把裤子穿上
So, you know, isn't there maybe
some way you and Sheldon could
会不会有一天你能和Sheldon
- compromise on this whole presentation thing?
- No, No.
- 在出席会议那件事上彼此妥协呢?
- 不会的 不会的
Scientists do not compromise.
科学家不会妥协
Our minds are trained to synthetize facts
我们的头脑是被训练来综合事实
and come to inarguable conclusions.
然后得出无可置疑的结论
Not to mention, Sheldon is back-crap crazy.
更何况 Sheldon是个驼背的疯子
What is this?
这是什么?
Oh, careful.
哦 小心点
That's my original series Battlestar Galactica flight suit.
那是我收藏的太空堡垒卡拉狄加
原版系列宇航服
Oh, why didn't you wear it on Halloween?
哦 怎么你都没有在万圣节穿过?
Because it's not a costume, it's a flight suit.
因为它不是戏服 它是宇航服
Ok, alright, moving on.
好吧 继续
Oh, wow. A paisley shirt.
哇 涡旋纹花呢衫
It goes with my corduroy suit.
那件是用来配我的灯芯绒西服
if you mean it should end up in
the same place, then I agree.
如果你觉得它该和那西服同归于尽
我也同意
Is this your only tie?
这是你唯一的一条领带?
Technically, yes. But, if you'll notice...
理论上来说 是的
但是 如果你能注意到...
It's reversible!
它是正反两面的!
So it works as two.
可以当两条用
Sweetie, I don't even think it works as one.
亲爱的 我觉得当一条用它都够呛
- Is this all your clothes?
- Eh, yeah.
- 这就是你全部的衣服了?
- 没错
Everything since the eighth grade.
八年级至今的全部衣服都在这儿了
- The eighth grade?
- My last growth sprout
- 八年级?
- 我最后发育的年龄
Ok, well, let's go back to the curdoroy suit.
好吧 还是选这套灯芯绒西服吧
- Great.
- Yeah.
- 棒极了
- 是啊
I said no. Put it down.
我说了不 把它放下
Hey Sheldon.
嗨 Sheldon
Hello Penny.
你好 Penny
Get anything good?
收到啥好东西了?
Just the latest copy of
Applied Particle Physics quarterly.
只是最新的应用粒子物理学季刊
Oh, you know, that is so weird
that yours came and mine didn't.
哦 那真是有点奇怪
你的到了可我那期还没来
It was a joke.
我在开玩笑
Yep.
是的
Tip you waitresses.
I'm here all week.
打赏你的服务员
我整星期都会在这里哦
Penny, just to save you from further awkwardness,
Penny 为了防止你进一步尴尬
know that I'm perfectly comfortable with
the two of us climbing the stairs in silence.
我并不介意
我们俩爬楼梯时保持沉默
Oh, yeah ok, me too. Zip it, lock it.
好 我也是
拉链拉上 锁住
Put it in your pocket.
放进你的口袋
- So, you and Leonard...
- Oh dear God...
- 那么 你和Leonard...
- 老天啊...
Little misunderstanding, huh?
一点小误会啊?
A little misunderstanding...?
一点小误会...?
Galileo and the Pope had a little misunderstanding.
伽利略和罗马教皇也有一点小误会
(伽利略因日心说被教皇迫害)
Anyway, I was talking to Leonard this morning
and I think he feels really bad about it.
不管怎样 今天早上我跟Leonard谈过
我感觉他很难过
How do you feel?
你有什么感觉?
I don't understand the question.
我不明白你的问题
I'm just asking if it's difficult
to be fighting with your best friend.
我只想问
跟自己最好的朋友作对 会不会很难?
I haven't thought about it like that.
我没有这么想过
I wonder if I've been experiencing physiological manifestations
我只是在想
这些无意识的情感波动
of some sort of unconscious emotional turmoil
会不会影响我的生理表现
Wait, what?
等等 你说什么?
I couldn't poop this morning.
今天早上拉不出大便
You should just talk to him,
I'm sure you guys can work this out.
你得找他谈谈 我肯定你们俩能和好
- Certainly preferable to my plan.
- Which was?
- 我的计划更可取
- 你的计划是?
A powerful laxative.
一服轻泻剂
You absolutely should talk to him.
你真该找他谈谈
Look, I know Leonard values you
as a friend and he told me himself
我知道Leonard当你是朋友
而且他自己说的 如果没有你的小点子
without your little idea there's no way
he could come up with this whole experiment thing.
他根本无法提出这个实验
Excuse me. "Little idea"?
对不起 "小点子"?
Yeah, I mean he tried to explain it to me,
是的 他试着跟我解释这个实验
- I didn't really understand it but...
- Of course you didn't.
- 我实在不明白 但是...
- 你当然不明白
He said: "Little idea"?
他说"小点子"?
Oh, well, no...
Not...
噢 不... 不是...
- Not in those words.
- In what words then, exactly?
- 不是那个词
- 那他是怎么说的?
Oh, you know... Gee. The exact words are...
It's more the spirit in which he said...
你知道的....确切的词是...
他说的更富有灵气...
- What did he say?
- You had a lucky hunch
- 他说了什么?
- 你有个幸运驼背
Hey, Sheldon, I've been thinking, instead of arguing about this...
嘿 Sheldon 我在想 与其争论...
Don't you ever speak to me again.
不要再跟我说话
What...?
什么...?
Ok, I'm leaving for the conference.
我要去参加会议了
Have fun presenting my "lucky hunch"
但愿你能尽情陈述我的"幸运驼背"
Shel, I didn't mean it like that.
Shel 我并不是这意思
- Then why did you say it?
- I don't know, I wasn't...
- 那你为什么这么说?
- 我不知道 我...
- Were you trying to impress Penny?
- No, no, not at all. A little bit.
- 你想逗Penny开心?
- 不 不 并不是 有一点
How did that work out for you?
那样真的有用吗?
- Leonard, ready to go?
- Libido: 1 Truth: 0.
- Leonard 准备好了吗?
- 性欲:1  真相:0
Ok, I'm gonna ask you one more time.
我再问你一次
We did the work together,
let's present the paper together.
我们一起做的研究
就一起去陈述论文吧
And I'm telling you for the last time,
我最后回答你一次
it's pandering, it's undignifying, and bite me.
这是在拉皮条 这是无地自容
有种咬我
Let's go.
我们走吧
- Bye Sheldon.
- Goodbye Penny.
- 再见 Sheldon
- 再见 Penny
One of these days... bshh!
总有那么一天...卟!
There you go.
可以了
You're right this side does look better.
你说的对 这一面的确好看点
No, no, I didn't say better, I said "less stained".
不 我并没说更好看
我说"少点污渍"
I just checked the house.
There's probably 20-25 people in there.
我刚刚检查了下房间
里面大约有20-25个人
- You're kidding!
- Is that all?
- 真的?!
- 就这么多?
"All?"
In particle physics 25 is Woodstock!
"就这么多?" 在量子物理学里
25人就是伍德斯托克音乐节
- Then good!
- I wasn't expecting such a crowd,
- 那很好!
- 我可没想到有这么多人
I'm all nervous.
我好紧张
It's ok, just open with a joke,
you'll be fine.
没事的 开头讲个笑话 会顺利的
A joke... Ok.
笑话...好吧
How about this? Um, ok...
这个怎么样? 呃 好吧...
There's this farmer
有个农夫
and he has these chickens but they won't lay any eggs, so...
他养了一群鸡却不会下蛋 于是...
he calls a physicist to help.
他找了个物理学家来帮忙
The physicist then does some calculations,
物理学家做了些计算
and he says: "I have a solution,
然后说 "我有个解决的办法"
but it only works for spherical chickens in a vacuum".
"但只对在真空环境下的球形鸡适用"
Right?
好笑吧?
Oh, sorry, I just had heard it before.
噢 对不起 我之前听过这个笑话
- Let's roll. Hey, nice suit.
- It's a classic, right?
- 我们进去 嘿 不错的西服
- 很经典 对吧?
I really should have brought my own car.
我真该自己开车来
So, in conclusion,
总而言之
the data show that at temperatures approaching absolute zero,
数据显示 当温度接近绝对零度时
the moment of inertia changes, and a solid becomes a supersolid,
惯性矩会改变 固体将变成超立体
which clearly appears to be a previously unknown state of matter.
也就是我们之前所未知的物态
Thank you!
谢谢!
- Are there any questions?
- Yeah.
- 有什么问题吗?
- 有
What the hell was that?
那是什么鬼东西?
Any other questions?
还有其他问题吗?
Doctor Sheldon Cooper here, I am
the lead author of this particular paper.
我是Sheldon Cooper博士
是这篇论文的主笔
Thank you.
谢谢
And you sir, you have completely skipped
over the part where I was walking through the park
而你 这位先生
你完全跳过了那段 -- 我穿过公园
and I saw these children on a
merry-go-round which started me thinking
看到孩子们在旋转木马上
about the moment of inertia in gases like helium
引起我思考当类似氦气的气体
at temperatures approaching absolute zero.
温度达到绝对零度时的惯性矩
I didn't skip it. It's just
an anecdote, it's not science.
我没有跳过 那只是个趣闻 并不是科学
Oh, I see. It was
the apple falling on Newton's head,
噢 我知道了
那是掉在牛顿头上的苹果
- was that just an anecdote?
- You are not Isaac Newton.
- 那只是个趣闻吗?
- 你不是艾萨克・牛顿
No, no, that's true. Gravity
would have been apparent to me without the apple.
不 不 这是真的
不用苹果 重力也能找到我
You cannot possibly be that arrogant.
你怎么能如此傲慢
You continue to underestimate me,
my good man.
你就继续低估我吧 伙计
Look, if you weren't happy with my presentation
then maybe you should have given it with me!
听着 如果你因为我的陈述而不愉快
也许你该跟我一起陈述!
As I have explained repeatedly,
unlike you,
我已经重复过好几次 跟你不同
I don't need validation from lesser minds.
我不需要那些没脑子的人来肯定我
No offense.
无意冒犯
Really, so why did you come?
真的? 那你为什么来?
Because I knew you'd screw this up.
因为我知道你会搞砸
I didn't screw it up!
我并没有搞砸!
Oh, please. I admit that spherical
chicken joke,
拜托 我承认那个球形鸡的笑话不错
- that was hilarious.
- Thank you.
- 很搞笑
- 谢谢
But it was straight downhill from there.
但从那以后就直线下滑
I've had enough of your condescendship.
我受够了你的鄙视
Maybe I didn't go to college
when I was 11 like you.
也许我没有像你一样 11岁就上大学
Maybe I got my doctorate at
24 instead of 16
也许我24岁才获得博士学位
而不是16岁
but you are not the only person
who is smarter than
但你不是唯一一个
everyone else in this room!
比这里在座各位聪明的人!
No offense.
无意冒犯
And I am clearly not the only person
而且我显然不是唯一一个
who is tormented by insecurity
被不安全感折磨
and has an ego in need of constant validation!
并需要被持续认可的自负的人!
So you admit you're an egotist?
你承认自己自负了?
Yes!
是的!
My name is doctor Leonard Hofstadter
and I can never please my parents so
我是Leonard Hofstadter博士
我永远取悦不了我的父母
I need all my self esteem
from strangers like you!
所以我需要从你们这些陌生人身上
找回自尊!
But he's worse!
但他更糟糕!
Ok, that's it!
好了 够了!
Stop it!
停下!
You cannot blow up my head
with your mind!
用你的意念弄不爆我的脑袋!
Then I'll settle for your aneurism!
那么我就让你生块动脉瘤!
- Stop it!
- You hit me!
- 停下!
- 你打我?!
You saw that he hit me!
你们看到了 他打我!
You tried to blow up my head!
你想弄爆我的脑袋!
So it was working!
那就是说有用咯!
It wa... It was not!
You're a nutcase!
没...没有用! 你是个疯子!
We'll see about that!
我们走着瞧!
Heads up, you people in the front row!
戴好头盔! 你们坐在前排的人
This is a splash zone!
这里是浪溅带!
Stop it!
住手!
Just quit it!
快住手!
Is this usually how these physics things go?
物理学通常都是发展成这样的吗?
More often than you think.
比你能想象的要多
You could have offered me a ride home.
你本可以载我一程的
You're lucky I didn't run you over.
没有轧死你 已经算你走运了
I really don't understand what you're so unhappy about.
真不知道你为什么这么不开心
You begged me to come, I came.
你求我去的 我去了
There's just no pleasing you.
你这人真难伺候
You're right, I'm the problem,
I'm the one that needs help.
你说的对 问题出在我身上
我才是需要帮助的人
Well, that's not much of
an apology but I'll take it.
好吧 虽然这算不上道歉 但我接受
Excuse me,
不好意思
is there anything you would apologise for?
你有什么需要道歉吗?
Yes.
有
I'm sorry I tried to blow up your head.
很抱歉我尝试弄爆你的头
It was uncalled for.
很不必要的举动
You won't believe this.
你们不会相信的
Somebody got the whole thing with their
cell phone and put it on YouTube!
有人用手机拍下了整个过程
并上传到了YouTube!
What?
什么?
- Who would do that?
- That would be me.
- 谁会这么干?
- 我会
Hey, check it out,
it's a featured video!
嘿 过来看看 还被置顶了!
He hit me!
You saw that he hit me!
他打我! 你们看见了 他打我!
[i]You tried to blow up my head![/i]
你想弄爆我的脑袋!
- Then it was working!
- It was not working! You're a nutcase!
- 那就是说有用咯!
- 没...没有用! 你是个疯子!
We will see about that!
我们走着瞧!
You people in the front row
heads up!
戴好头盔! 你们坐在前排的人
This is splash zone
这里是浪溅带
Stop it! Leave it,
leave it!
住手! 放下! 放下!
You want a volcano nerve pinch!
让你尝尝火神力量钳!
(出自"星际漫游")
You should clip your fingernails!
Those hurt!
你该剪指甲了! 抓痛我了!
Oh, Jeez. does this suit really look that bad?
天啊! 这件西服真有那么难看呀?
Forget your suit,
look at my arms waving.
别提你的西装了
看看我的手臂晃动
I'm like a flamingo on Ritalin.
我像是吃了利他林(中枢兴奋药)的火烈鸟
Howard,
Howard
would you like to explain to me
why your Facebook page
能跟我解释下 为什么你的相册里
has a picture of me sleeping
on your shoulder captioned
有我靠在你肩膀睡觉的照片
"me and my girlfriend"?
标题为"我和我的女朋友"?
Uh oh, here comes
the talk.
啊哦 质问来了
- You hit me!
- You tried to blow up my head!
- 你打我!
- 你想弄爆我的脑袋!
- So it was working!
- It was not working! You're a nutcase!
- 那就是说有用咯!
- 没...没有用! 你是个疯子!
We will see about that!
我们走着瞧!
Somewhere in China
中国某处
What losers
混蛋东西嘛
Yeah Gigantic American geeks
对啊 很大的书呆子
who's doing that?
谁在搞鬼?
Someone from Pasadena,
California named...
一个来自加州帕萨迪纳的叫...
"Wolowizard"
Wolowizard
Awesome!
牛!
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
proudly presents
-------------------------------
本论坛字幕仅翻译交流学习之用
禁止任何商业用途否则后果自负
-------------------------------